This is so cool!
new interns yeah working them hard yeah yeah well what do you think guys are
you working hard hard I think I deserve we deserve surprise you want a surprise
yeah okay all right so hey my surprise could be in an umbrella oh sorry I
actually borrowed his umbrella and I forgot it I'm sorry I'm sorry Beto I
will invite you for lunch okay all right so um today we're gonna be looking at
your favorite movie that's why you guys are invited today this movie that is the
new like rave between youngsters Twilight that's right so it's a vampire movie it's
a aim towards like it's kind of like a softer version of interview with the
vampires oh no definitely you cannot even compare right this is obviously there's
a big thing going on with all the vampire phenomenon you know so they have a true
blood which is a series and that's like for more adults and this Twilight is
actually they made the movie out of books it's a saga it's called the Twilight
saga all right so there are three move three books total right for four of the
saga and basically we have a young vampire named Edward who lives with his
family in this very small town in the United States Edward Colin right and his
family chose to not drink human blood mm-hmm they're kind of like vegetarians
yeah it's true they say that it's like the vegetarians of vampires because they
don't feed on human blood so it's like tofu so what do they eat that just the
animals oh so they feed on animal blood yeah they usually go to some hunting
trips and then they feed off bears I think yes they like bears it's true all
right and well between or among this family of vampires this girl Bella Bella
Bella isabella she comes into play because she recently moved to the
neighborhood and she is like kind of falling in love with this vampire because
he's so mysterious well yeah the thing that is weird about this movie it's not
weird the thing that was new about this movie is that they brought this world you
know where it's always vampires and so we start and they're evil and they're
like and they put it into high school so it was really smart like marketing wise
it was very smart because it's they can actually go outside in the in the
daylight but if their son they can't you know because it has to be cloudy yes it
has to be cloudy that's why they live in Seattle because it's always raining
exactly so it's very it's funny like so it's kind of like high school musical
but with vampires yes except that there's no singing and dancing and why
would it be high school musical if there's no singing oh it's like very
teenager II and very Disney like all right so and that's basically the gist
of it but of course there's a problem of course there's a there's something going
on and there's other there are other vampires who are actually evil and they
do eat people yeah so Edward is trying to protect the girl well well imagine like
they meet this you know Bella network and she knows that he's different so
they start this amazing relationship where he cannot have her because he wants
to eat her you know like kill her that can pose a problem for any relationship
exactly so it's like it's very difficult so that's why it's so good because Edward
he's like handsome and powerful and immortal and he's like 300 years old or
something so and he can read people's minds oh yeah this is why she's so
special yes all right so mini Lily what do you think of them you liked it why do
you love it because don't tell me because the actor is like handsome I don't know
actually I read the four four of the books you love the books yeah so it's
kind of like a new Harry Potter like last last decade or well five years ago it
was all about Wizards and magic and now it's all about vampires okay so four
books and it's like do the books get actually more interesting than the
first one because honestly for me the movie was really boring really I thought
it was boring why and I thought it was tacky Twilight yeah well like alright so
the guy the vampire he's a little bit more mature cuz he's like 90 years old
or whatever but the girl she's like a typical 17 year old who thinks she knows
what she wants and she's like you know take me drink my blood I want to become
a vampire too I love you it's just like well actually in the books when you're
reading them it gets to a point that it's like a little bit annoying well for
me because all the story is like yeah I love you no I love you more no I love
you more so it's kind of like boring yeah the whole story is like really good so
it is a love story we have to keep that in mind and it's aimed towards teenagers
more right yeah well it's like the modern Romeo and Juliet now it's like forbidden
everyone is against it but they love each other like so much that is ridiculous you
know so I think that's why it's being such a big success because it has all
the components they're American first of all they're like handsome they're rich
they're in high school so it has the right mix for teenagers what Brian what
do you think of the movie I didn't like the movie why it seemed boring for me as
well I read the first book and I liked it more because it left me to imagine more
things and all the ambient and maybe because I have a little bit of a
darker mind I could see it like developing darker like a dark vampire
something like interview with the vampire something like a drag or Dracula I can
see all the environment going on like something just dark and when I saw the
movie I just didn't seem kind of disappointed me a bit but at the same
time when I was reading the movie certain things were more interesting and
had more of an excitement to it like the like the whole they are some action
scenes right where where they are they're fighting between vampires or the
there's a scene where they're playing baseball and they're like they have
their superpower so they're running really fast yeah and again so if I think
about it in a dark way then I can imagine all these things like being even
more even being bloodier or whatever bloodier you want more blood you want
well not exactly but then when he does I have a dark mom okay not exactly it's
just that when I saw the movie it seemed that it didn't really have a climax and
that nothing was really special about it yeah it didn't really have a climax the
ending well because it's the first book yeah I guess yeah so but I think it I
mean all the movie it's pretty good I mean I liked it so you like the movie yeah
I did like it I don't think it's like the best thing I've ever seen but it's
very entertaining you know and when you want to just like watch a movie where he's
all about love and how pretty and young they are so I think it's a it's a good
movie to just like spend some time but it's not like amazing what was your
favorite scene in the movie my favorite scene you know every moment my favorite
moment is when she comes in the classroom and he smells her and he wants
to puke and you like that but I love that part I love that scene I don't know
because he looks like so annoyed you know like he's he wants to puke and like
they intend it's intense because she's like looking at him and his eyes are like
black and weird bloodshot and then she's like smelling her armpits exactly
exactly so I think it's funny and then he just gets up and leaves and she's
like yeah I kind of like the I like the part when she visits his house his
house is really cool and how he lives and stuff then they went upstairs and
also that scene when he saves her I think that was kind of cool that's a cool
scene in the car in the car and he just stops it with one hand yeah that's a cool
scene that was a cool part and the baseball game and the baseball game was
cool and they always play when it's thunder because that's how hard they're
yeah yeah I like also the part when they go up you know the trees beautiful
imagine if you can do that yeah I thought that the the special effects
weren't very good well the thing is that this movie actually was very
low-budget really yeah they thought it was gonna go directly to DVDs yeah
because there there weren't any any really famous actors in no no and also for
example Robert Pattinson which is Edward Cullen he's a British and when he
applied for the job like nobody wanted him they were like God no he's not
right for the part should be an American but at the end it was like great
success but he didn't have a British accent in the movie no he plays an
American Wow yeah no he used to play in Harry Potter really yeah who did he
play well I have one of the guys he was like an extra no no no of course not he
was one of like the main characters in one of the yes he was there oh yeah so
now he's he's huge in the state and the second movie has more budget they
changed the director before he was a woman now they change it to this guy
more money into it so I don't know I hope they don't spoil so the new one is
coming out soon right I think it's so in November we can we can watch the second
one called new moon new moon all right interesting I think it was it was an
alright movie but definitely it's a it's a movie more towards girls yeah it's a
girly movie it's a chick flick and but it wasn't very interesting for me I was
very disappointed because there was a lot of hype going around it I don't know
how they created so much hype and anticipation and excitement because
everyone was talking about it people were downloading the soundtrack and it's
teenagers remember they said they said the standard so that's why you should
never follow what the trend yeah so cuz then when I finally watched it I was
like I mean it was alright I actually I really enjoyed the soundtrack it was
pretty cool yeah but the movie itself I personally give it a C plus C plus what
do you give it a B B B I'd also give it a C plus I don't know maybe it's because
I'm more I'm not so into vampires but I'm more into werewolves okay how about
the second one has world and I'll look at that all right so if you guys have
any other suggestions for movies that we can take a look at please send us an
email or comment on our website English pot calm and our email address is
English pot at Praxis language calm and next time we'll be looking at a classic
film yeah well not a classic but a film that came out about 10 or 15 years ago
okay that's not a classic I'm sorry well it's not new it's not like a new
blockbuster but it's a film that's considered among the top of all time
we don't know we'll let you know next time all right so I will see you guys
next time